<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kunal Nagar</title>
    <link>http://kunalnagar.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kunal Nagar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kunalnagar.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube to Mp3 converter</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/youtube-to-mp3-converter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/youtube-to-mp3-converter/</guid>
      <description>So my parents listen to music on YouTube. Because apparently, services like Saavn or Gaana don&amp;rsquo;t make sense to them. And honestly, I can&amp;rsquo;t blame them. They&amp;rsquo;re gonna use what seems familiar to them.
One day they asked me - how can I download this song to my phone and listen to it without opening the YouTube app? And I suggested numerous YouTube to Mp3 converters on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My horrible experience with ACT Fibernet</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/act-fibernet-horrible-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/act-fibernet-horrible-experience/</guid>
      <description>Note: Contains more cursing than usual. Reader discretion is advised.
May 13, 2015 - I move to an apartment in Bangalore to start my new job and get my own high speed internet connection, or as the cool kids say - Fibernet connection. I was so happy. I mean, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you be if you got this kind of a speedtest?
 What real happiness looks like #ACT #Fibernet 😳</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rewrite WordPress Multisites</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/rewrite-wordpress-multisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/rewrite-wordpress-multisites/</guid>
      <description>Recently, one of my tasks was to create a Blog and a Knowledge Base and use similar credentials and login-flows for both of their Admin Consoles. Without a doubt, WordPress Multisite is the perfect choice for this since you don&amp;rsquo;t have to manage your Auth/Settings/Dashboard in multiple places.
Note: Creating WordPress multisites is out of the scope of this article. For more info, check out this link.
When you set up a WordPress Multisite install, you create one root site and then all other multisites are created as subfolders (children).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shared Modules using RequireJS</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/shared-modules-using-requirejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/shared-modules-using-requirejs/</guid>
      <description>Every application needs a set of modules that are shared across all other modules. Things like String/Array helpers, Loggers etc are used across your application and it makes sense to create wrappers around them and expose them via a Common Module.
Before we start, I&amp;rsquo;m assuming that you know a bit about RequireJS. If not, I suggest you visit their website and learn about AMD (Asynchronous Module Definition).
Here is the basic folder structure that we&amp;rsquo;re going to follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copy Path Widget using ZeroClipboard</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/github-style-copy-path-zeroclipboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/github-style-copy-path-zeroclipboard/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will be creating the Clone Widget on GitHub that allows you to copy a Repo URL by clicking a button. It works natively in Chrome and falls back to Flash in Firefox &amp;amp; Safari. If Flash is not installed, the Copy button is not shown, but the user can still select the path and copy it manually.
Here is how the widget looks natively in Chrome (Copy button enabled)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TripMode - Your Mobile Data Savior</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/tripmode-mobile-data-savior/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/tripmode-mobile-data-savior/</guid>
      <description>TripMode is the best way to stop updates and other background processes from consuming your mobile data. It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect companion for people who travel a lot and need to keep their mobile data under control.
TripMode automatically reduces your mobile data consumption when you use a mobile hotspot thus saving you data and money. It has been designed to be as simple as possible and is accessible at any time from the system tray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bartender 2 for Mac OS X</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/mac-bartender-os-x-menu-bar-minimalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/mac-bartender-os-x-menu-bar-minimalism/</guid>
      <description>Bartender 2 for Mac OS X is an amazing piece of software that allows you to de-clutter your OS X Menu Bar. You can organise your menu bar apps by moving or rearranging them or moving them to the Bartender Bar.
Features Here are some of the top features:
 Lets you tidy your menu bar apps how you want. See your menu bar apps when you want. Hide the apps you need to run, but do not need to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Browse YouTube like a boss</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/chrome-extension-youtube-jukebox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/chrome-extension-youtube-jukebox/</guid>
      <description>YouTube is great. I use it all the time to learn, relax, listen to music and probably have a laugh or two. So I built a Chrome Extension that is a lighter version of YouTube Playlists.
It adds two things to youtube.com:
 An &amp;ldquo;Add to Jukebox&amp;rdquo; button next to every video A Sidebar for consuming videos and making a list  As soon as you activate the extension, you’ll see an “Add to Jukebox” button next to every video on YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom 404 Pro</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/custom-404-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/custom-404-pro/</guid>
      <description>Custom 404 Pro is a WordPress plugin that allows users to override the default 404 page with any page from the WordPress Dashboard. You can even redirect users to a different URL everytime you get a 404. It has 8,000+ active installs as of August 2016.
While this may sound trivial to many developers, I built this for people who are less technical and don&amp;rsquo;t know how to write PHP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ionic Push Notifications</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/ionic-push-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/ionic-push-notifications/</guid>
      <description>Setting up push notifications in a hybrid mobile app can be a challenging task if you don’t know the mechanics of it. Fortunately, Ionic’s ngCordova service allows us to handle push notifications easily. This article assumes that you have a basic understanding of Hybrid Mobile Applications and how to deploy them to an Android device. If not, I will try and mention the steps explicitly when I can. Please also note that this is not a Getting Started Tutorial for Ionic and you need to have a development environment setup beforehand with the Android SDK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix RDSRV Malware (VSearch/Downlite)</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/fix-rdsrv-malware-vsearch-downlite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/fix-rdsrv-malware-vsearch-downlite/</guid>
      <description>The past week has been an absolute disaster for me as far as Web Security is concerned. My Macbook Pro picked up an adware from some shitty website that would not show up in most Adware Removal Tools. It was after a lot of research and thanks to Thomas from The Safe Mac that I managed to fix the problem. In this article, I will guide you through the process and how I realised that the problem was not on my Mac, but in my Modem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Laravel 5 on OS X</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/install-laravel-5-on-os-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/install-laravel-5-on-os-x/</guid>
      <description>Note: I originally wrote this article on Medium.
If you&amp;rsquo;re like me, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably spent countless hours on the web trying to figure out how to install the dev-develop version of Laravel on your machine. As of today, the latest Laravel version 4.2 but if you want to see the awesome Laravel 5 features, you need to upgrade.
In this article, you will learn how to setup Laravel 5 from scratch on OS X.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Multiple SSH Keys on a Mac</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/setup-multiple-ssh-keys-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/setup-multiple-ssh-keys-mac/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to setup multiple SSH keys on your mac. This can be useful when you need multiple accounts (may be for personal use or work) to be setup on a single mac.
 Video Notes Generating SSH Keys (Github Article)
Boilerplate Text for Config file: Host testgithub HostName github.com User git IdentityFile ~/.ssh/id_rsa_testgithub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix Google Drive Dark Mode Icon</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/fix-google-drive-dark-mode-icon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/fix-google-drive-dark-mode-icon/</guid>
      <description>If you are using Dark Mode for the Dock in OS X Yosemite, then you will notice that the Google Drive icon is hardly visible. In fact, some of you might not even notice it and think that Google Drive isn’t working at all.
Here is a simple script that you can download and run from your terminal. Right-Click and save the file on your Desktop. Make sure to keep the file extension as .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Laravel 5 on GoDaddy Shared Hosting</title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/deploying-laravel-5-on-godaddy-shared-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/blog/deploying-laravel-5-on-godaddy-shared-hosting/</guid>
      <description>Note: I originally wrote this article on Medium.
So your awesome project is ready for deployment and you need to set it up on GoDaddy shared hosting servers.
Requirements Here are some things that you need before we get started:
 A GoDaddy shared hosting account SSH Access Awesome Laravel Project to be deployed  Steps Before we start, let’s assume that your home directory on the server is</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://kunalnagar.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kunalnagar.in/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>